Register of the Christopher Temple Emmet Papers 1913-1974
Hoover Institution Archives
- RADIO BROADCAST TRANSCRIPTS, 1939-1973
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, November 9, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, November 16, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, November 23, 1945
  - "Crisis in China," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 27, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, December 7, 1945
  - Untitled, Forum, December 11, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, December 14, 1945
  - "What Causes Peace?" Queens College Forum, WNYC, December 18, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, December 21, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, December 28, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, January 4, 1946
  - "Prospects for Unity in China," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, January 9, 1946
  - Untitled, Freedom House Forum, WEVD, New York, January 18, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, January 24, 1946
  - Untitled, January 25, 1946
  - Untitled, February 1, 1946
  - "Problems Facing the New French Government," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 5, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, March 15, 1946
  - "The Manchurian Crisis," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 19, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, March 22, 1946
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 2, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, April 5, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, April 19, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 10, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 17, 1946
  - "Mihailovich: Hero or Traitor?" The Reviewing Stand, Northwestern University on the Air, WGN, Chicago, June 9, 1946
  - "Can General Marshall's Mission Succeed?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 25, 1946
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, July 9, 1946
  - "Behind the Mihailovich Case," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, July 23, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, August 9, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, August 16, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, September 13, 1946 (Box 122)
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, September 17, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, September 20, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, September 27, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, October 4, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, October 11, 1946
  - "De Gaulle and the French Constitution," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 15, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, October 17, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, October 25, 1946
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 29, 1946
  - Untitled, November 1, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, November 8, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, November 15, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, November 22, 1946
  - "Hopes for a United States of Europe," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 26, 1946
  - "How Can Capitalist America Best Do Business with Socialist or Communist Europe?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 10, 1946
  - "Iran and Henry Wallace," WEVD, New York, December 13, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, December 20, 1946
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, January 3, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, January 10, 1947
  - Untitled, January 17, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, January 24, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, January 31, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, February 7, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, February 14, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, February 21, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, February 28, 1947
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 4, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, March 7, 1947
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 13, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, March 21, 1947
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 1, 1947
  - "Should the Communist Party Be Banned?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 15, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, April 18, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, April 25, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 16, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 23, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, June 6, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, June 13, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, June 20, 1947
  - "Does the Marshall Plan Conflict with the Truman Doctrine?" WEVD, New York, July 4, 1947
  - Untitled, July 11, 1947
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, July 25, 1947
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, August 12, 1947
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 7, 1947
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 4, 1947
  - "Shall We Include China in the Marshall Plan?" Forum, WEVD, New York, December 2, 1947
  - "Year End Review of Foreign Policy," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 30, 1947
  - "Lincoln and Gandhi," WEVD, New York, February 12, 1948
  - "Soviet Citizen Abroad," Forum, WEVD, New York, September 7, 1948
  - "China," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 8, 1948
  - Untitled, January 14, 1949
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 11, 1949
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 3, 1950
  - "German-American Misunderstandings," NWDR, Hamburg, July 4, 1950
  - "Attitudes towards German Rearmament," WEVD, New York, September 20, 1950
  - "Alternative to Appeasement in Korea," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 8, 1950
  - "Mr. Hoover's Plan," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 22, 1950
  - Untitled, Forum, 1951
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 13, 1951
  - "Can the Chinese People Liberate Themselves?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 25, 1951
  - "Is Tito a Reliable Ally?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, September 28, 1951
  - "A New Message to the Enslaved Countries," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 12, 1951
  - "Problem of McCarthyism," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 9, 1951
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 1, 1952
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 15, 1952
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 6, 1952
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, October 31, 1952
  - "Finland," Forum, May 29, 1953
  - "The Suez Crisis," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, September 28, 1956
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 12, 1956
  - Untitled, November 1956(?)
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, January 18, 1957 (Box 123)
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 15, 1957
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 29, 1957
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 10, 1957
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 24, 1957
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, September 27, 1957
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 11, 1957
  - "The Soviet Threat to Turkey," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 25, 1957
  - "40th Anniversary, Bolshevik Revolution," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 8, 1957
  - "The Dispute with France over Arms to Tunisia," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 22, 1957
  - "Was NATO Conference a Success?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 20, 1957
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, 1958
  - "Crisis in Indonesia," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, January 3, 1958
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, January 31, 1958
  - Untitled, University of the Air, WEVD, New York, February 14, 1958
  - "Foreign Aid: Crucial Issue, 1958," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 28, 1958
  - "The Franco-Tunisian Conflict," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 28, 1958
  - "The Role of Vietnam in Southeast Asia," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 11, 1958
  - "France in Crisis," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 25, 1958
  - "Is Indonesia Going Communist?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 9, 1958
  - Untitled, June 6, 1958
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, September 26, 1958
  - "Is Inspected Disarmament Possible?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 10, 1958
  - "The Polish and Hungarian Revolutions," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 23, 1958
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 7, 1958
  - "The U.N. Debate on Hungary," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 5, 1958
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 19, 1958
  - "The Meaning of the Mikoyan Visit," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, January 16, 1959
  - "The Balance of Power in the Cold War," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, January 30, 1959
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 13, 1959
  - "De Gaulle's Policy in Algeria," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 27, 1959
  - "Can We Solve the European Refugee Problem?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 13, 1959
  - Untitled, March 27, 1959
  - "Results of the NATO Meeting in Washington," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 10, 1959
  - "Are the Allies United?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 24, 1959
  - "The Geneva Foreign Ministers Conference," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 22, 1959
  - "The Mystery of Khrushchev's Visit to Albania," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 5, 1959
  - "Why Did Adenauer Change His Mind?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 19, 1959
  - "Hungary and the United Nations," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 4, 1959
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, January 12, 1960
  - "Algeria," WEVD, New York, January 27, 1960
  - "Soviet Techniques of Propaganda and Subversion," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 12, 1960
  - Untitled, February 26, 1960
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Broadcast, WEVD, New York, March 11, 1960
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Broadcast, WEVD, New York, March 25, 1960
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Broadcast, WEVD, New York, May 3, 1960
  - "The Tyrol," October 21, 1960
  - "Foreign Policy in the Campaign," WEVD, New York, November 4, 1960
  - "U.N. Assembly Session," November 25, 1960
  - "An Appraisal of the U.N. Session," University of the Air, Foreign Policy Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 16, 1960
  - "The Diplomatic Break with Cuba," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, January 13, 1961
  - "The U.N. and the Congo," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 10, 1961
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 24, 1961
  - "How Communist Is Castro?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 7, 1961
  - "France After the Generals' Revolt," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 5, 1961
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 19, 1961
  - "Tractors for Prisoners," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 1, 1961
  - "The Berlin Crisis and the Hungarian Revolution," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 25, 1961
  - "Congo and Katanga," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 11, 1961
  - Untitled, Barry Gray Show, November 20, 1961
  - "Should Communist China Be Admitted to the U.N.?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 24, 1961
  - "The U.N. in Crisis," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 22, 1961
  - "Indonesia and New Guinea," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 16, 1962
  - "The U.S. Involvement in South Vietnam," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 2, 1962
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 16, 1962
  - "Britain and the Common Market," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 26, 1962
  - "How Solid Is Democracy in Western Germany?" WRVR, New York, March 27, 1962
  - Untitled, University of the Air, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 1962
  - "The U.S. Partnership with the Common Market," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 10, 1962
  - "The Refugee Deportations from Hong Kong," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 25, 1962
  - "Do We Have a 'No-Win' Foreign Policy?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 8, 1962
    Use copy reference number: 74105_a_0005492
    The guests are Adolf A. Berle, Jr., former Assistant Secretary of State, and Eugene Lyons, senior editor, Readers Digest. Emmet moderates. The men debate whether the Kennedy policy is a "no win" policy. Lyons is critical of the administration while Berle defends its policy. Alternate title: "What Is Our Cold War Policy?"
  - "First Hand Reports from Berlin," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, September 28, 1962
    Use copy reference number: 74105_a_0005493
    The guests are Walter Kirschenbaum, assistant commissioner of licenses of New York City, who had just returned from East and West Berlin, and Norbert Muhlen, foreign correspondent and syndicated writer for North American Newspaper Alliance. Emmet moderates. This program was the season premier. A short portion of an unrelated program is also on the tape.
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 12, 1962
    Use copy reference number: 74105_a_0005494
    The guests are - Moshe Decter, writer on foreign affairs and former managing editor, New Leader, and Michael Harrington, author of "The Other America" and editor, New America. Emmet moderates.
  - "The Prospects for Atlantic Unity," Foreign Affairs Roundtable program October 26, 1962
    Use copy reference number: 74105_a_0005495
    This program concerns the introduction of the United Kingdom into the Common Market. The guests are Dr. Kurt Birrenbach, member, Foreign Affairs Committee of German Parliament, and William Diebold, director, Economic Studies, Council on Foreign Relations. Emmet moderates.
  - "Cuba and the Election," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 9, 1962
  - "Impact of Cuba on Latin America," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 7, 1962
  - "Hungary," Forum, WEVD, New York, December 21, 1962
  - "The Congo Kaleidoscope," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, January 18, 1963
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 29, 1963
  - "Cuba," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 12, 1963 (Box 124)
  - "Political Impact of the Dollar Deficit," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 26, 1963
  - "The Italian Elections," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 10, 1963
  - "New U.S. Policy toward Hungary," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 23, 1963
  - "East-West Trade," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 7, 1963
  - "Diem and Viet Nam," WEVD, New York, November 15, 1963
  - "Kennedy's Foreign Policy Legacy," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 29, 1963
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 13, 1963
  - "Balance Sheet of Freedom," WEVD, New York, December 27, 1963
  - "The Growing Crisis in Southeast Asia," WEVD, New York, January 10, 1964
  - Untitled, January 24, 1964
  - "The Crisis in East Africa," February 1964
  - "De Gaulle and China," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 7, 1964
  - "A New Western Policy towards Eastern Europe," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 20, 1964
  - "Vietnam," WEVD, New York, April 3, 1964
  - "The New Phase of the Berlin Crisis," WEVD, New York, June 8, 1964
  - Untitled, September 22, 1964
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, September 25, 1964
  - "Vietnam," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 6, 1964
  - "Russia after Khrushchev," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 3, 1964
  - "The Real Choice in Vietnam," WEVD, New York, December 4, 1964
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, January 28, 1965
  - "U.S. Foreign Policy and World Opinion," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 1, 1965
  - Untitled, April 30, 1965
  - "Vietnam, Latin America and Communists," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 13, 1965
  - "Soviet Anti-Semitism," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 14, 1965
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 5, 1965
  - "British Policy and the United Nations," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 3, 1965
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, January 26, 1966
  - Untitled, February 8, 1966
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, February 11, 1966
  - "The Record of Coalition Governments with the Nazis, Fascists, and Communists," WEVD, New York, March 3, 1966
  - "A Coalition in Vietnam?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 10, 1966
  - "Germany and the United Nations," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 23, 1966
  - "China Policy," April 4, 1966
  - "The Crisis in NATO," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 7, 1966
  - "Developments in the Dominican Republic," WEVD, New York, May 5, 1966
  - "Two Eyewitness Reports on Vietnam," WEVD, New York, May 19, 1966
  - "The Tenth Anniversary of the Hungarian Revolution," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 11, 1966
  - "The Manila Conference and Its Effect on the Elections," WEVD, New York, November 8, 1966
  - "The German Elections," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 12, 1966
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, January 9, 1967
  - "Communist Reforms in Yugoslavia," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 9, 1967
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, July 12, 1967
  - "U.S.I.S," August 16, 1967
  - "A Year End Review of Foreign Policy," WEVD, New York, December 20, 1967
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, March 11, 1968
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, April 8, 1968
  - "The World Student Unrest," WEVD, New York, June 11, 1968
  - "Yugoslavia," WEVD, New York, December 2, 1968
  - "Germany and the New Administration," WEVD, New York, January 22, 1969
  - Untitled, March 3, 1969
  - "France after de Gaulle," WEVD, New York, May 5, 1969
  - "New Perspectives for European Unity," WEVD, New York, June 2, 1969
  - "The Impact of the German Elections," WEVD, New York, October 6, 1969
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, November 3, 1969
  - "The Vietnam Labor Movement and the Vietcong," WEVD, New York, December 1, 1969
  - "Prospects for 1970," WEVD, New York, January 5, 1970
  - "French Policy and the Middle East," WEVD, New York, March 4, 1970
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 8, 1970
  - "Cambodia," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 6, 1970
  - "The Crisis in the Middle East," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 3, 1970
  - "Will Vietnamization Work?" WEVD, New York, October 7, 1970
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, January 6, 1971
  - "NATO Today," WEVD, New York, April 7, 1971
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 5, 1971
  - "The Dollar Deficit," WEVD, New York, June 2, 1971
  - "Red China and the United Nations," WEVD, New York, November 3, 1971
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, November 30, 1971
  - "The Crisis in Pakistan," WEVD, New York, December 1, 1971
  - "Yugoslavia," WEVD, New York, January 5, 1972
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, February 2, 1972
  - "University Youth and Foreign Policy," WEVD, New York, April 5, 1972
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 3, 1972
  - "China: Then and Now," WEVD, New York, June 7, 1972
  - "The World Drug Traffic: Can the Epidemic Be Stemmed?" WEVD, New York, October 4, 1972
  - "Issues in the German Election," WEVD, New York, November 1, 1972
  - "Will There Be a Bloodbath in Vietnam?" WEVD, New York, December 5, 1972
  - "Is It Peace with Freedom?" WEVD, New York, February 5, 1973
  - "Will Yugoslavia Survive Tito?" WEVD, New York, April 4, 1973
  - "Germany," WEVD, New York, May 2, 1973
- RADIO BROADCAST PHONOTAPES 1953-1973
  Phonotapes of radio broadcasts, arranged chronologically (1 reel per entry unless otherwise noted).
  - Untitled, undated (11 reels) (Box 125)
  - "Anti-Americanism in Germany," undated
  - "British Policy in the U.N.," undated
  - "Fifth Amendment," Barry Gray Show, undated
  - "Korean Prisoners of War" December 1-3(2 reels)
    Use copy reference number: 74105_a_0000460 (side A), 74105_a_0000469 (side B), and 74105_a_0000470
    Year of recording unknown. U.N. Minan India on Korean POWs
  - "Youth and Foreign Policy," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, undated
  - Various recordings, April 18-May 29, 1953
  - "India's Role in Peace Conference" and "Should We Offer Non-Aggression Pact to Soviet Russia?" WEVD, New York, November 13, 1953
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, February 25, 1954
  - Untitled, Face the Nation Program, October 9, 1955
  - "East-West Trade," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, January 20, 1956
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 25, 1956
  - Various recordings, March 15-May 24, 1957
  - "Indonesia," April 26, 1957
  - "Shall We Continue Aid to Tito?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 6, 1957
  - "Results of the NATO Meeting," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 20, 1957
  - Untitled, Cedric Foster Show, WOR, New York, March 7, 1958
  - "The Role of Vietnam in Southeast Asia," Foreign Affairs Forum, WEVD, New York, April 11, 1958
  - "France in Crisis," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 25, 1958
  - "The Communist Threat in Indonesia," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 9, 1958
  - "Will de Gaulle Come to Power?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 23, 1958
  - "Economics of the Cold War," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 6, 1958
  - "Prospects for Disarmament," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 10, 1958
  - "Anniversary of Polish and Hungarian Revolutions," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 24, 1958
  - "The U.N. Debate on Cyprus," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 21, 1958
  - "The U.N. Debate on Hungary," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 5, 1958
  - Untitled, Ray Heatherton Show, WRCA, December 15, 1958
  - "Soviet Threat in Berlin," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 19, 1958
  - "The Meaning of the Mikoyan Visit," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, January 16, 1959
  - Untitled, January 30, 1959
  - "Problems of a New Berlin Airlift," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 13, 1959
  - "Can We End the European Refugee Problem?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 13, 1959
  - "De Gaulle's Policy on Algeria," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 27, 1959
  - "Results of the NATO Meeting in Washington," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 10, 1959 (Box 126)
  - "Are the Allies United?" Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 24, 1959
  - "Tibet's Impact on Asia," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 8, 1959
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 22, 1959
  - "Khrushchev's Visit to Albania," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 5, 1959
  - "Why Adenauer Changed His Mind," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 19, 1959
  - "Foreign Repercussions of Khrushchev's Visit," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, September 25, 1959
  - "Adenauer's Visit to England," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 20, 1959